Guide to the Richard Earl Fikes Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Audio-Visual and Electronic Materials, Series 6
  - Bluebonnet: An Expert Help System, CSDG talk, 1982 Nov 23; 32.1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 32)
  - Richard Fikes and Austin henderson, Klone/CSDG Talk, 1980 Jul 22; 32.2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 32)
  - Artificial Intelligence, Undated; 32.3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 32)
  - Software Architecture, Undated; 32.4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 32)
  - Photographs and transparencies: (Box 33)
    13 (12 inch. X 10 inch.) photographs (A Commitment-Based Model of Office Work for Expert Office System, 1982) 7 transparencies (Building Knowledge-Based Systems) 19 transparencies (The Monkey Problem, etc.)
- Miscellaneous material, Series 7
  - Name Cards (Box 30)
  - Desktop diary, 1971-74, 1976-77, 1979, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Address & Phone Directories / Pocket Day-Timer Notes (Box 31)
- Computer files, Series 8
  - Email, 1997-2007
    - 1991 emails
    - 1992 emails
    - 1993 emails
    - 1994 emails
    - 1995 emails
    - 1996 emails
    - 1997 emails
    - 1998 emails
  - Private Sector
    - Test, 1991
    - Acuitus - Acuitus develops computer-based tutoring systems.
    - TomAndAndy
    - AF Rome
    - CelCorp
    - IKRIS
    - AdIn
    - Bradshaw
    - CNRI
    - iSpring
    - JonesDay
    - HAR
    - Meanings
    - TPIN Number_files
    - Woodside Labs
    - Yahoo!
    - YY Software
  - Stanford University
    - Teaching and Administration
      - CS222– Knowledge Representation. Lecture presentations, projects, examinations., 1997-2004
        Folder: C:\Documents and Settings\pchan3\Desktop\Fikes\Series 3 Stanford University\Teaching and Administration\CS222\ FILE 216,118 airport.pdf 6/24/2008 15:25 FILE 162,008 airport.ps 6/27/2002 11:22
        - 1997
        - 1998
        - 2000
        - 2001
        - 2002
        - 2003
        - 2004
      - CS Department
        - AI Qual
        - Gates - Office Space
        - ISYS - The Intelligent Systems Laboratory
          - MSCS Advising
        - MSCS Admissions
        - PhD Admissions
        - Ron Brachman
        - Seibel PhD Fellowship
        - Miscellaneous
      - Annual Faculty Reports, 1998-2005
      - Professor (Research) Reappointment files
      - Retirement - Files related to Fikes' retirement
      - Students' CV, thesis, etc.
      - Miscellaneous
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory
      - Finances - Lab Budgets, Financial Analysis, etc.
      - KSL Seminar
      - Management - Performance Appraisals, Recruitments, Personnel Matters, Work Distributions, etc.
      - Projects
        - How Things Work
        - KD-D
        - KnOWS
        - KSL with other Corporations and Agencies
          - Agnosco
          - Cisco
          - CTC
          - IBM
          - NASA
          - NSA
          - PARC
          - Sony
          - VerticalNet
        - Projects from Funding Agencies
          - ARDA
            - AQUAINT
            - NIMD
            - IKRIS
            - CASE
          - Darpa
            - Aggregation
            - Cognitive Systems
            - HTW
            - IAO
            - IPTO
            - ISAT
            - ISO_Panel
            - ISO_Simulation
            - ITE
            - Programs
              - ASSIST
              - CALO
              - DAML
              - EELD
              - HPKB
              - I3
              - Info_Brokers_Project
              - REAL
              - RKF
              - UltraLog
            - SBD
            - SEC
            - Strategic Knowledge Bank
            - Miscellaneous
          - DHS
          - ERC
          - Livermore Labs
          - NSF
          - Vulcan
        - Technologies
          - Agents
          - GlobalInfoBase
          - Inference Web
          - JTP
          - Knowledge Sharing
          - Ontologies
          - TAP
          - UIMA
      - Talks
        - Agnosco
        - AQUAINT
        - Brokers
        - DHS Text Analysis Workshop
        - HTW
        - I3
        - Integration
        - ISAT
        - KD-D
        - KnOW
        - KR&R
        - KSL
        - MARS
        - NASA
        - OKBC
        - Pfizer_Visit
        - REAL
        - Semantic Web
        - SHADE
        - Spring Symposia
        - UltraLog
        - Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous
  - Professional Organization Activity
    - AAAI Admin
    - Professional Meetings
      - ISWC
      - KR
      - OKBC
      - QAS
    - DARPA IPTO REAL-Gambit Workshop, 2002 Nov 18-20